HiringCat AI QA - Create Job
Running: Create Job
Using saved authenticated browser session.
Step 1: Open New Job UI and type the unique job title.
STEP: Typed job data on visible form - title=AI QA E2E Job ms4fq16z-1, slug=ai-qa-e2e-ms4fq16z-1
Step 2: Save/publish the active job with exact payload.
REQUEST: API POST /api/jobs - {"title":"AI QA E2E Job ms4fq16z-1","slug":"ai-qa-e2e-ms4fq16z-1","department":"QA Automation","location":"Remote","employmentType":"full_time","status":"active","description":"AI QA E2E Job ms4fq16z-1 created by HiringCat AI deep E2E...","thankYouMessage":
PASS: API response POST /api/jobs - HTTP 201; {"id":"7bd8c7f7-f353-491c-8863-d8860121eb88","orgId":"5413bea4-80e3-4d78-b9cd-7933e5db4632","title":"AI QA E2E Job ms4fq16z-1","slug":"ai-qa-e2e-ms4fq16z-1","description":"AI QA E2E Job ms4fq16z-1 created by HiringCat AI deep E2E...","department":"QA Automa
Opening created job detail page and verifying title is visible.
Verifying created job persisted as active through authenticated API.
REQUEST: API GET /api/jobs/7bd8c7f7-f353-491c-8863-d8860121eb88 -
PASS: API response GET /api/jobs/7bd8c7f7-f353-491c-8863-d8860121eb88 - HTTP 200; {"id":"7bd8c7f7-f353-491c-8863-d8860121eb88","orgId":"5413bea4-80e3-4d78-b9cd-7933e5db4632","title":"AI QA E2E Job ms4fq16z-1","slug":"ai-qa-e2e-ms4fq16z-1","description":"AI QA E2E Job ms4fq16z-1 created by HiringCat AI deep E2E...","department":"QA Automa
Result: PASS - Created and verified active job "AI QA E2E Job ms4fq16z-1" (ai-qa-e2e-ms4fq16z-1).